Pavlos Papadopoulos | Front-End Web Developer







LinkedIn



+306993751715



F_mail



Thessaloniki, Greece

Front-End Web Developer, with industry experience building websites and web applications. Translate UX / UI designs to actual code. Also, maintain updated knowledge of new trends and technology. Ability to convert complex ideas into React projects along with Redux and testing with Jest and Enzyme. Delivering solutions using Next.js combined with a headless CMS.

Experience _

Front-End Web Developer

EXEO LP

May 2019 - Present Thessaloniki, Greece

Technologies:

- ➤ ASP.NET Core / DevExtreme UI components
- CSS (Sass) / Bootstrap
- JavaScript (jQuery, Knockout.js)

Freelance Web Developer

December 2020 - Present

- > Building a website-blog for a medical professional
- > Technologies: Next.js / Strapi headless CMS / Sass

Skills.

- ➤ HTML5 / CSS3 (Sass)
- JavaScript (React.js / Next.js, Redux, jQuery, Knockout.js)
- Testing (Jest / Enzyme)
- Bundlers (Webpack, Parcel)
- Version Control (Git / TFVC)
- Platforms (Netlify, AWS)

Projects .

- Order Management System (React.js / Redux / Jest / Enzyme)
- Portfolio Page (Next.js Netlify, Ghost headless CMS AWS)
- React App (time machine) My article on dev.to
- React App (video finder)
- Website Layout (globTaste)

Education ———

University of Thessaly - <u>MASTER'S DEGREE</u>: AUTOMATION IN AGRICULTURE **Aristotle University** - BACHELOR'S DEGREE: AGRICULTURAL ENGINEERING

2007 - 2012

1999 - 2006

Languages .

English: Cambridge First Certificate In English, Level B2 **Spanish:** State Certificate of Language Proficiency, Level B1